quantummf.com 2016-03-15

# Quantum’s Privacy Policy

                                  Quantum’s Privacy Policy
The following privacy policy is provided by the Quantum Asset Management Company Private
Limited, Quantum Trustee Company Private Limited and Quantum Mutual Fund, subsequently
all are commonly called as Quantum in the whole Policy.
Our commitment to you:
As a Quantum investor, you have entrusted to our care not only your hard-earned money but
your personal and financial data as well. We recognize that your relationship with us is based
on trust, and that you expect us to act responsibly and in your best interests. Because your
personal and financial data are your private information, we hold ourselves to the highest
standards for their safekeeping and use.
This means, most importantly, that we do not buy or sell investor or prospective investor
information—whether it is your personal information or the fact that you are or may become a
Quantum investor—to anyone or from anyone except that we share data that is required to be
shared statutorily.
Instead, we use your information primarily to complete transactions that you request or to
make you aware of our / other financial products and services (including those of group
companies) that we offer.
The information we collect about you:
You provide personal information when you complete a Quantum account / transaction
application physical / electronic mode which includes fax, fax-email, email, Social Messaging,
Short Messaging Services (SMS) and Interactive Voice Response (IVR) etc. Notwithstanding the
completion of transaction, the personal information / data for transaction provided by you
electronically will be stored.
                                                                                             1

  You also provide personal information when you request literature or newsletters or any
  information about our products or services or a transaction that involves Quantum.
   In addition to the personal information that you provide to us directly, we may receive
  information about you indirectly on the basis of your authority to third parties to provide your
  information / data to us. We may also obtain personal information from third parties in order
  to verify your identity, address, to prevent fraud, to meet regulatory requirements or to help us
  identify products and services that may benefit you. We may collect your browser information
  to help us to identify product and services that may benefit you.
  Personal information collected from any source may amongst many things include, your name
  and address, Permanent Account Number, Aadhaar number, Date of birth, mobile number,
  email id, the details of occupation, income, KYC Compliance, bank accounts, any Proof of
  Identity and Proof of Address.
  How do we handle your personal information:
  We do not buy or sell information about current or former investors or their accounts to / from
  third parties. Nor do we share information about investors or prospective investors, except
  when needed to complete financial / non- financial transactions at your request or to make you
  aware of related financial / non-financial transactions, products and services that we or our
  group companies offer. Here are the details:
    In order to complete certain transactions that you direct, it may be necessary to provide
     identifying information to companies, individuals, or groups that are not affiliated with
     Quantum. For example, if you transfer funds from the bank to Quantum, we will need to
     provide certain information about you to your bank to complete the transaction.
    In certain instances, we may contract with affiliated or nonaffiliated companies to perform
     services for us. Where necessary, we will disclose information we have about you to these
     third parties. In all such cases, we provide the third party with only the information necessary
                                                                                                    2

    to carry out its assigned responsibilities, and only for that purpose. And we require these
    third parties to treat your private information with the same high degree of confidentiality
    that we do.
   We will maintain the record of your personal / transaction information for processing and
    authentication of transactions, review of quality of services and data validation purpose for
    the period of time as may be required by the relevant laws and statutes.
   We may send messages / SMS or call to intimate / verify / authenticate Transactions even if
    your number is registered with the National Do Not Call Registry (NDNC).
   We will maintain the record of your personal information for any the period of time as may
    be required by the relevant laws and statutes even after you cease to be our investor.
   All the personal information collected in the physical application / electronic form will be
    stored, recorded and available with our Registrar & Transfer Agent and such information shall
    be used by the Registrar & Transfer Agent only as stipulated by us to process your financial /
    non-financial transactions and to disclose to meet regulatory requirements. The Registrar &
    Transfer Agent is required to treat your private information with the same high degree of
    confidentiality that we do.
   Finally, we will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are compelled by
    law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to prevent fraud, to
    Income Tax authorities, data as required under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act and
    Information Technology Act etc. or on the directions of any other statutory authority).
How do we protect your privacy online:
  Our concern for the privacy of our investors naturally extends to those who use our website
  www.QuantumAMC.com / www.QuantumMF.com
   Our website uses some of the most secure forms of online communication available,
    including data encryption, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, and user names and
    passwords. These technologies provide a high level of security and privacy when you access
    your account information or initiate online transactions.
                                                                                                   3

    www.QuantumAMC.com/ www.QuantumMF.com offers customized features that require
     our use of "HTTP cookies" and similar data files—tiny pieces of information that we ask your
     browser to store. However, we make very limited use of these data files. We don't use them
     to pull data from your hard drive, to learn your e-mail address, or to view data in cookies or
     other similar data files created by other websites. We will not share the information in these
     data files or give others access to it—except to help us better serve your investment needs.
    When you visit our website, we may collect certain technical and navigational information,
     such as computer browser type, internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time
     spent on our website. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software
     compatibility issues or to resolve technical or service problems, or it may be analyzed to
     improve our web design and functionality and our to improve our ability to serve you and
     your accounts.
    In certain cases, we may use third-party service providers to place advertisements for us on
     other websites, and to help us measure the effectiveness of our online advertising. These
     service providers may use cookies and web beacons, tiny invisible graphics that contain
     unique identifiers, to collect limited technical, web navigation, and other information, such as
     the advertisement presented, IP address, operating system and browser type, and pages
     visited or generated on our site etc. We do not provide any personally identifiable
     information about our users or clients to these service providers, and they do not collect such
     information for us.
  How would we safeguard your personal information:
  Within Quantum, we restrict access to information about you to those Quantum employees
  who need to know the information in order to perform their jobs, such as servicing your
  accounts or notifying you of various products and services. To protect your personal
  information, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in keeping with
  industry standards and best practices, and we review and adjust these safeguards regularly in
  response to advances in technology.
                                                                                                    4

Our Registrar & Transfer Agent also ensures that your data information is made available to
those of its employees who need to know the information in order to perform their jobs, such
as servicing your accounts. To protect your personal information, our Registrar & Transfer
Agent also maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in keeping with industry
standards and practices, and they review and adjust these safeguards regularly in response to
advances in technology.
What you can do:
    For your protection, we strongly recommend that you do not provide your account
     information, user name, password, or Personal Identification Number (PIN) or Telephone
     Personal Identification Number (TPIN) to anyone, not even to any representative from
     Quantum. Your right to use the Quantum website / any electronic channels of transaction is
     not transferable. Any password, right to access given to you is solely for your own purpose
     and that is not transferable. When you have completed your electronic transaction, it is
     advisable to sign out from your account and close your browser window, cut off the phone,
     etc in order to prevent others from potentially retrieving your confidential information; if
     you share a computer with someone or are using a computer from any public domain.
If you become aware of any suspicious activity relating to your account, it is your responsibility
to contact us immediately at CustomerCare@QuantumAMC.com or call us on our Toll free no.
180022-3863.
Quantum reserves its right at any time, to modify, alter, change or amend this privacy policy at
its sole discretion and the then modified or amended Policy will be uploaded on the website.
By using our website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of us processing
your personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not
agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may not use our website. Your continued use of
our website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy shall mean that you also
accept those changes.
                                                                                                   5
